I want you to tell me
the truth about Joffrey.
He's a monster.
With the Tyrells beside us, no one
will think of rebelling for another century.
Ser Dontos of House Hollard.
Ser Meryn, help Ser Dontos
celebrate my name day.
It would be bad luck to kill a man
on your name day.
You'll be my new fool!
Thank you, Your Grace.
Do you know
what it takes to unite 19 clans?
I told them we were all going to die
if we don't get south.
Let us go, and my father will pay you
whatever you want.
Enough to buy me a new head?
_
We need to find Sansa Stark a husband.
Tyrion'll do as he's bid,
you'll marry Ser Loras.
— I am not some brood mare...
— You're my daughter!
My feelings for you have not changed.
I'm not your lady,
I'm your whore.
He's a crow, he'll stab us in the back.
Kill him!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net